Guide to the City Theatre Company Records, 1973-1993 CTC.1991.01
ULS Archives & Special Collections
City Theatre Company Records
1973-1993
ULS Archives & Special Collections
City Theatre Company (Pittsburgh, Pa.)
CTC.1991.01
10.5 Linear Feet (25 boxes)
The City of Pittsburgh created its own theatre company in 1974 called The City Players. In 1979, the City Players relocated to the University of Pittsburgh and became the City Theatre Company (CTC). This collection contains operational files, correspondence, scripts, production photos, etc., documenting the activities of the CTC from its creation until its move to the South Side of Pittsburgh in 1991.
History
The City of Pittsburgh created its own theatre company in 1974. This company, The City Players, was a troupe that resided in the newly renovated Allegheny Public Theatre on the North Side (now the Hazlett Theatre of the Pittsburgh Public Theatre) and contained a troupe of young professionals that reached out into the community by offering free performances of new plays and classics. The City Players were financed through the Comprehensive Employment and Training Act (CETA) and administered by Pittsburgh's Citiparks Department.
In 1979, the company relocated to the University of Pittsburgh and became the City Theatre Company (CTC). The CTC co-produced the inaugural season of the Three Rivers Shakespeare Festival. Both organizations eventually became separate entitites, however, the Three Rivers Shakespeare Festival continued to hire actors and directors from CTC from time to time. In 1980, Pitt assisted in renovating a campus building into a 117 seat theatre space which became known as The New City Theater. Pitt also continued to provide financial support until the severance of the relationship in 1988.
Despite the evolution from a touring troupe to a resident professional company, the CTC continued to provide touring productions as a vital part of its' operation. Tours reached approximately 35,000 children, senior citizens, and other people each year. Local playwrights or the acting company usually wrote the scripts for the touring shows.
In 1988 The City Theatre Company ended its' artistic and financial relationship with the University of Pittsburgh and became a completely independent theatre company. In the summer of 1991, CTC moved into their new quarters located at 57 South 13th Street in the South Side neighborhood of Pittsburgh.
Related Material
Ford E. and Harriet R. Curtis Theatre Collection of Pittsburgh Theatre Programs, 1840-present, CTC.1966.01, Curtis Theatre Collection, Archives & Special Collections Department, University of Pittsburgh Library System
Arrangement
The City Theatre Company Records are organized into six separate series. All files are arranged alphabetically. Additional scope and content notes are found after the series titles.
Series I. Operational Files, 1975-1988
Series II. Playscripts
Series III. Photographs
Series IV. Oversize Materials
Series V. Additional Operational Files, 1991-1994
Scope and Content Notes
The City of Pittsburgh created its own theatre company in 1974 known as The City Players. In 1979, the City Players relocated to the University of Pittsburgh and became known as the City Theatre Company (CTC). This collection contains operational files, correspondence, scripts, production photos, etc. showing the activities of the CTC from its creation until its move to the South Side neighborhood of Pittsburgh in 1991.
Access Restrictions
No restrictions.
Acquisition Information
These records were a gift of the City Theatre Company in July 1991.
Previous Citation
City Theatre Company Records, 1973-1993, CTC.1991.01, Curtis Theatre Collection, Special Collections Department, University of Pittsburgh
City Theatre Company Records, 1973-1993, CTC.21, Curtis Theatre Collection, Special Collections Department, University of Pittsburgh
Theater -- Pennsylvania -- Pittsburgh; Theater; Performing arts -- Pennsylvania -- Pittsburgh; College theater -- Pennsylvania -- Pittsburgh; Pittsburgh (Pa.) -- Intellectual life; South Side (Pittsburgh, Pa.) -- Intellectual life; North Side (Pittsburgh, Pa.) -- Intellectual life; Theater programs; City Players (Pittsburgh, Pa.); City Theatre Company (Pittsburgh, Pa.)
- Operational Files, 1975-1990; I.
  Scope and Contents note
  These materials consist of the daily business files, correspondence, production memos, internal reports, minutes, etc. of the City Theatre Company. The files are arranged in alphabetical order. Files concerning City Theatre productions are followed by the date of the season in which they were performed.
  - Actor's Equity Association - Contracts (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Actor's Equity Association - Correspondence, 1985-1987 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Actor's Equity Association - Deputy forms (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Actor's Equity Association - Grievance and benefit Forms (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Actor's Equity Association - Membership program (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Actor's Equity Association - Salaries, 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Actor's Equity Association - Small Professional Theatre Contract (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Agents - New York (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Artists in Education - Pennsylvania Council on the Arts (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Attendance reports (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Audio-visual return receipts (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Auditions - 1985/86 season (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Auditions - Cold reading (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Beggar's Opera - Press, 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Board of Advisers (Box 1, Folder 15-17)
  - Board of Advisers - Correspondence, 1983-1987 (Box 1, Folder 18-20)
  - Board of Advisers - Fundraising, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Board of Advisers - Meeting minutes, 1983-1986 (Box 1, Folder 22-24)
  - Board of Advisers - Meeting minutes, 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Bouquet Street Theatre Agreement with the University of Pittsburgh (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Box office reports, 1982-1988 (Box 2, Folder 3-8)
  - Budget, 1981-1987 (Box 2, Folder 9-14)
  - Budget, 1987-1990 (Box 3, Folder 1-3)
  - By-Laws, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Canterbury Tales - Press, 1980-1981 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Children of a Lesser God - Press, 1983-1984 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Children of a Lesser God - Program printing, 1983-1984 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Chinaman's Whisper - Press, 1978-1979 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - The Circus - Schedules and memos, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Citiparks Playworks (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - The City Theatre Blues (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Tamer of Horses - Press, 1987-1988 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Clarence Darrow - Press, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - The Comeback, 1977-1978 (Box 3, Folder 14-15)
  - Concessions reports, 1982-1984 (Box 3, Folder 16-17)
  - Contact sheets (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Contracts, 1981-1986 (Box 3, Folder 19-22)
  - Corporate sponsorship (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence, 1975-1981 (Box 3, Folder 24-27)
  - Correspondence, 1981-1986 (Box 4, Folder 1-5)
  - Fan mail from school tour, 1985-1988 (Box 4, Folder 6-8)
  - Creative Advancement Awards (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Crimes of the Heart, 1984-1985 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Curse of the Starving Class, 1981-1982 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Curse of the Starving Class - Schedules and memos, 1981-1982 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Custodial schedules (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Danger: Memory! - Contracts, 1987-1988 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Danger: Memory! - Press, 1987-1988 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Danger: Memory! - Production rights, 1987-1988 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Danger: Memory! - Schedule and memos, 1987-1988 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - The Danube, 1984-1985 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - The Day of the Picnic, 1983-1984 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Death and Life of Sneaky Fitch - Contracts, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Death and Life of Sneaky Fitch - Press, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Death and Life of Sneaky Fitch - Props list, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Doctor Inspite of Himself - Budget, 1975-1976 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Doctor Inspite of Himself - Budget and press, 1975-1976 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Donations, 1984-1987 (Box 5, Folder 1-6)
  - Donations In Kind (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Dracula, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Drop Out! (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Employee Records, 1981-1982 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - The Final Hour, 1977-1978 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - The Final Hour - Prop receipts, 1977-1978 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - The Final Hour - Tour schedule, 1977-1978 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Five Year Plan, 1985-1989 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Fool for Love, 1983-1984 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Forms (Originals) (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - La Forza d'Amore, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - La Forza d'Amore - Schedules and memos, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Foundation for the Extension and Development of the American Professional Theatre (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Fund Raising (Mike Vargas), 1987 (Box 6, Folder 13-14)
  - Gateway to Music, including Fan Mail and Outdoor Advertising, 1981-1987 (Box 6, Folder 15-23)
  - Glengarry Glen Ross - Contracts, 1986-1987 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Glengarry Glen Ross - Contracts and press, 1986-1987 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Glengarry Glen Ross - Contracts, schedules, and memos, 1986-1987 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Good Evening - Press, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Good Evening - Press, schedules, and memos, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Grant Prospects, 1984-1985 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Harry and Claire, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Hartwood - Contracts, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Hartwood - Contracts and reports, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Hartwood - Contracts, schedules, and memos, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 10-11)
  - High School Tour, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - History, 1975-1986 (Box 7, Folder 13-14)
  - How I Got that Story, 1982-1983 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Howard Heinz Endowment (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - The Hypochondriac, 1984-1985 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Illusions of Fantasy - Schedules and memos (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Incommunicado - PR postcards, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Indians - Correspondence, 1981-1982 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Indians - Correspondence and press, 1981-1982 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Internal Revenue Service status letters (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Internship, 1982-1983 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Interpreted Performances (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Inventories - miscellaneous (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Job Descriptions (City Players) (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Josephine: The Mouse Singer - Contracts, 1984-1985 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Josephine: The Mouse Singer - Contracts, schedules, and memos, 1984-1985 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - LadyHouse Blues, 1982-1983 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Leadership Pittsburgh (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Let's Misbehave - Benefit invitations (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Letters of Recommendation (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Living Stage Theatre Company (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Loose Ends, 1981-1982 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Lovers and Keepers - Contracts, 1986-1987 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Lovers and Keepers - Contracts and press, 1986-1987 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Lovers and Keepers - Contracts, schedules, and memos, 1986-1987 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Managing Director Prospects (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Mary Miller Dance Company (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Master Schedule, 1982-1988 (Box 8, Folder 7-9)
  - Masterson, Marc (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - May Performing Arts Festival, House Manager's Report, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - May Performing Arts Festival, House Manager's Report -- Pennsylvania Council for the Arts Grant, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Mid-Atlantic States Arts Consortium (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Misanthrope, 1978-1979 (Box 8, Folder 14-16)
  - Mobile Hymn, 1982-1983 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - National Conference on State Humanities Programs, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - New Play Series, 1986-1987 (Box 8, Folder 19-20)
  - Newsletter (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Nuts, 1985-1986 (Box 8, Folder 22-24)
  - On the Verge, 1986-1987 (Box 8, Folder 25-26)
  - Organizational chart (City Players) (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Organizational Planning (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Painting Churches, 1985-1986 (Box 9, Folder 1-2)
  - Painting It Red, 1988-1989 (Box 9, Folder 3-4)
  - Parking - Forbes Quad (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Patron opinion forms, 1984-1985 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Pennsylvania Arts Coalition (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Pennsylvania Council on the Arts - Advisory panel (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Pennsylvania Council on the Arts - Barbara Feige salary roposal [Denied] (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Pennsylvania Council on the Arts - Grant proposals, 1981-1984 (Box 9, Folder 10-11)
  - Pennsylvania Local Arts Network (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Perfect Party, 1986-1987 (Box 9, Folder 13-14)
  - Peter Pan, 1977-1978 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Pitt/CTC Agreement (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Pittsburgh Cultural Trust (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Pittsburgh Cultural Trust - Arts Organizations mailing list (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Pittsburgh Foundation - Grant proposals, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Pittsburgh Playback Theatre - Pittsburgh AIDS Task Force benefit, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Pittsburgh Stage - Fireproof certificate (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Plays considered, 1983-1984 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Principia Scriptoriae, 1987-1988 (Box 9, Folder 23-25)
  - Productions rights (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Profile, 1983-1986 (Box 10, Folder 1-2)
  - Provost's Day (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Puss n' Boots, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Red Keds, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Rehabilitation Institute of Pittsburgh (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Resource Connections (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Resumes and head shots - Female actors/performers (Box 10, Folder 8-9)
  - Resumes and head shots - Male actors/performers (Box 10, Folder 10-11)
  - Resumes - Administration/Technical (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Resumes - Designers (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Resumes - Directors (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Robin Goodfellow - Swashbucklers, 1981-1982 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - La Ronde, 1980-1981 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Rose Cottages, 1987-1988 (Box 11, Folder 4-7)
  - San Francisco Mime Troupe (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - School contact information (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Scriptshare - New Dramatists (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Separate Incorporation budgets, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Sesame Street, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Shadow, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Staff meeting minutes, 1984-1985 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Staff Time Records (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Steel City, 1975-1976 (Box 11, Folder 16-17)
  - Story Theatre, 1980-1981 (Box 11, Folder 18-19)
  - Subscription brochures (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Survey of Performance Accessibility for People with Handicaps in NonProfit Professional Theatres in America (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Swashbucklers, 1980-1981 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Table Manners, 1978-1979 (Box 11, Folder 23-25)
  - Talking with..., 1984-1985 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Tamer of Horses, 1987-1988 (Box 11, Folder 27-30)
  - Telecommunications (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Theatre Association of Pennsylvania (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Theatre Communications Group (Box 12, Folder 2-3)
  - Theatre rentals (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Theatrical structure (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Three Rivers Shakespeare Festival (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Time sheets (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - TIX Booth (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Toad of Toad Hall, 1975-1976 (Box 12, Folder 9-10)
  - Tours, 1978-1979 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Tour sheets (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Tuesday, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 13-14)
  - Understudy policy (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - University of Pittsburgh Department of Theatre Arts - Production calendar, 1986-1987 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - University/Resident Theatre Association (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - U.R.T.A./A.E.A. Rules (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Volpone, 1977-1978 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Wings, 1980-1981 (Box 12, Folder 20-23)
  - Waiting for Lefty, 1977-1978 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Work/Study Information (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Working, 1982-1983 (Box 12, Folder 26-27)
- Playscripts, II.
  The scripts that are included in this series appear to be plays that were produced, considered for production, or submitted for consideration. They are filed in alphabetical order by title. Included with each production title is the name of the author.
  - Acting Up! (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Ah, Youth by E. Fried (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - All Together Now by E. Pawlikowsky (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Assistant Warden by B. Pribram (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Beauty and the Beast by M. Brill (adaptation) (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Benya the King by R. Schotter (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Careless Husband (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Chinaman's Whisper by C. Peters (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Cocoon by E. Fried (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Creeps by D. Freeeman (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Diviners, the by J. Leonard (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Drop Hammer by E. Fried (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Dying to Make It (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Elegy for Stanley Gorski by E. Fried (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Factwino Meets the Moral Majority by SF MimeTroupe (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Foolin' Around with Infinity by S. Dietz (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Flying Doctor, the by S. Wyman (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Futures by M. Green (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Hopscotch (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - I Just Ate My Brain by T. Cumella (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - In the Woods by P. Freundlich (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Juketime in Duckberg by L. McCullough (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Legend of Sleepy Hollow, the by F. Gaines (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Misanthrope by Moliere (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Misanthrope [Stage Manager's Prompt Book] by Moliere (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Missing Links [Director's Promptbook] by A. Favorini (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - No Where to Go But Home by C. Cortazzo (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Passing Time by T. Cumella (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Postcards (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Principia Scriptoriae by R. Nelson (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Railroad Rag: A Workingman's Entertainment by J. Van Sickle (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - ReadyGetSet by C. Solomon (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Red Keds by H. Leroy (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Romeo and Juliet (scenes) - anon adaptation (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Saloon Society by B. Manville (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Second Beginning by E. Fried (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Some Things Can't Be Repaired (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Steel City [Act III] by A. Favorini (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Strider by M. Rozovsky (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Subway to Topeka by R. Meredith (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Stuff as Dreams Are Made On: A Shakespeare Collage, A Sandoe-DondioSuch (compiled by) (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Table Manners (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Table Manners [Director's Prompt book] (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Take Her Up Tenderly (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Tamer of Horses [Director's Prompt book] by W. Mastrosimone (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Toad of Toad Hall(adaptation) by K. Grahame (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Tomorrow is a Lonely Lady (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Trial, the (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Used (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Unicorn in the Garden (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Volpone by B. Johnson (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Waiting For Lefty (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Wedding Reception in the Pineapple Room (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Who Would Write Something Like That? (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Wizard of Oz (Box 16, Folder 21)
- Photographs, 1975-1987; III.
  Boxes 19 and 20 contain photos of productions, actors, and various shots of the theater. Box 21 contains negatives of some of the same photographs.
  - Photographs, 1.
    - Androcles and the Lion, 1. (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Beggar's Opera, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Beshinich, 'Smokey' George (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Bus Stop, 1977 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Children of a Lesser God, 1983 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Children's Tour, 1986-1987 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Chinaman's Whisper, 1979 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Performance Classes (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Clay People (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Comeback, 1978 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Crimes of the Heart, 1984 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Curse of the Starving Class, 1981 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Danube, 1985 (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - Day of the Picnic, 1985 (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - Death and Life of Sneaky Fitch (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - Dracula, 1975-1977 (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - Fool for Love, 1984 (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - La Forza D'Amore / The Circus, 1978 (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - General - Unidentified, 1978 (Box 17, Folder 19)
    - General - Unidentified rehearsal photos, 1978 (Box 17, Folder 20)
    - Gladys (Box 17, Folder 21)
    - Greater Tuna (Box 17, Folder 22)
    - Hawthorne, Myrenna (Box 17, Folder 23)
    - Hazlett Theatre (Box 17, Folder 24)
    - Hopscotch (Box 17, Folder 25)
    - How I Got That Story, 1983 (Box 17, Folder 26)
    - Hypochondriac, 1985 (Box 17, Folder 27)
    - Indians, 1982 (Box 17, Folder 28)
    - Janet Gillespie and Present Co. (Box 17, Folder 29)
    - Jefferson, David Louis (Box 17, Folder 30)
    - Josephine: The Mouse Singer, 1984 (Box 17, Folder 31)
    - Ladyhouse Blues, 1983 (Box 17, Folder 32)
    - Lavi, Gay Heit (Box 17, Folder 33)
    - Loose Ends, 1982 (Box 17, Folder 34)
    - Miles, Barry/Kloss, Eric (Box 17, Folder 35)
    - Mobile Hymn, 1983 (Box 17, Folder 36)
    - Muffly, Ann (Box 17, Folder 37)
    - Noah and the Arc, 1977 (Box 17, Folder 38)
    - Ozanam Strings (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Perfect Party, 1987 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Pinsker, Allan (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Principia Scriptoriae, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Real Inspector Hound, 1977 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - La Ronde, 1979-1980 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Sesame Street Fire Safety Show (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Staff - Miscelanneous including ballgame (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Stein, Mary Margaret (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Table Manners, 1979 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Toad of Toad Hall, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Trial, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Unidentified - Resume shots (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Volpone (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - Wen, Ming-Na (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - Wings, 1980-1981 (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - Working, 1982 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Negatives, 2.
    - Children of a Lesser God (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Children's Tour, 1986-1987 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Classes - Miscellaneous (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Comeback, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Curse of the Starving Class, 1981 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Day of the Picnic, 1984-1985 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Death and Life Sneaky Fitch, 1975 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Dracula, 1976-1977 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - La Forza / The Circus, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - General - Rehearsal, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - General, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Hypochondriac, 1984-1985 (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Indians, 1981-1982 (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - LadyHouse Blues, 1982-1983 (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - Loose Ends, 1981-1982 (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - Mobile Hymn, 1982-1983 (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - Noah and the Ark, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 17)
    - Real Inspector Hound, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 18)
    - Staff - Including ballgame (Box 19, Folder 19)
    - Toad of Toad Hall, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 20)
    - Trial, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 21)
    - Unidentified (Box 19, Folder 22-23)
    - Volpone (Box 19, Folder 24)
    - Wings, 1980-1981 (Box 19, Folder 25)
    - Working, 1982 (Box 19, Folder 26)
- Additional Operational Files, 1979-1993; IV.
  Scope and Content Notes
  This addition, donated in February of 1999, contains another series of operational files. The first series of operational files in this collection ran through 1991, this set contains operational files from 1991-1993, with a small amount of material from before 1991. This series is filed alphabetically by folder title and contain the daily business files, correspondence, production memos, internal reports, minutes, etc.
  - 70 Scenes of Halloween, 1992-1993 (Box 20, Folder 1-4)
  - Act Without Words - House reports (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - American Buffalo - Reviews/Articles, 1989-1990 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Audio Tapes - Reviews, 1992 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Baltimore Waltz - Press releases (see also NAMES Project), 1992-1993 (Box 20, Folder 8-9)
  - Bricklayers, 1991-1992 (Box 20, Folder 10-14)
  - Cabaret Verboten, 1992-1993 (Box 20, Folder 15-17)